janieandjack.com 2019-06-07

# Privacy Rights

#### Effective March 15, 2019

Janie and Jack values you as a customer ("you") and is committed to respecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use, share and disclose the personal information we collect at the website owned and operated by Janie and Jack (" **Site** "). Please note, we may use facilities outside of your home country to process, store or back up electronic information as further describted below. If you have any questions about this policy or whether it applies to you, please contact us at [privacy@janieandjack.com](mailto:privacy@janieandjack.com). 

BY PROVIDING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO JANIE AND JACK OR OTHERWISE USING OUR SITE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS POLICY AND OUR WEBSITE TERMS OF USE. 

Who We Are  
The Information We Collect and Use  
Additional Purposes For Which We Collect And Use Information  
When We May Share Information With Others  
Your Online Choices  
How We Protect Children's Privacy  
Links to Third Party Site  
Managing Your Communication Preferences  
Your California Privacy Rights  
Accessing and Updating Your Information  
Processing in the United States  
For EU Residents  
Changes to this Policy  
How to Contact Us  

#### Who We Are

When we use the term " **Janie and Jack** " or " **we** ," " **us** ," or " **our** ," we mean to refer  collectively to Janie and Jack, including Janie and Jack, LLC, and Janie and Jack Outlet. Janie and Jack is a member of the Gap Inc. family of brands. 

#### The Information We Collect and Use

When we use the term " **Personal Information** " we mean information that can or could be used to identify you as an individual person. We collect Personal Information through your use of our Site. Personal Information is referred to as Personal Data in some countries. We collect and use three categories of information and discuss each in turn below. 

  1. **Personal Information You Provide To Us**

We collect personal information when you choose to share that information with us in the following ways.

    * On our Site where you can register for an account, we collect contact and registration details (for example, name, username, password, address, phone number, and email address), which we use to administer the account and communicate with you.
    * When you sign up for our newsletter, we collect your contact information and communication preferences, which we use to manage how we communicate with you.
    * When you make purchases through our Site, we collect payment information and related shipping and transaction details, which we use to fulfill orders, complete your transaction and deliver products to you as may be ordered.
    * When you take surveys and enter challenges, promotions, contests and sweepstakes, we collect contact, demographic and eligibility information, which we use to confirm eligibility, administer the programs and communicate with you about awards.
    * When you submit identifiable comments or other content on the Site, we collect whatever information you supply and use this information to communicate with you if requested, and otherwise fulfill the purpose of the content submission. Please be aware that any stories, photos or comments that you submit on a public forum will become publicly accessible.
    * When you send gift certificates or refer a friend to our Site, we will collect the name and contact information of the recipient in order to fulfill your request.
    * If you submit a job application with Janie and Jack online, we will collect information including your contact details, work history, employment needs and interests, and anything relevant to the job for which you are applying. 

  2. **Information Collected Automatically**

We use various data collection technologies to collect other types of data that do not directly reveal your identity (" **Other Information** "). If we associate Other Information with Personal Information, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**Logging Functionality:** As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, internet service provider, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp and/or clickstream data. We generally only use this data for purposes such as security, fraud detection, and protecting our rights. 

**Cookies and Other Data Collection Technologies:** We and our subsidiaries, business partners, and service providers use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to manage our website and email messages and to collect and track information about you and your activities online over time and across different website. These technologies help us to recognize you, customize or personalize your shopping experience, store items in your online shopping cart between visits, and analyze the use of our Site to make them more useful to you. These technologies also allow us to, and allow us to allow our service providers to, aggregate demographic and statistical data and compilations of information, which may or may not include Personal Information, and provide this information to our service providers.

Most Internet browsers allow you to remove or manage cookie functions and adjust your privacy and security preferences. For information on how to do this, access the "help" menu on your Internet browser, or visit <http://www.aboutcookies.org/how-to-control-cookies/>. Please note, however, that disabling our cookies may result in your inability to take full advantage of all of the features of our Site.

**Analytics:** We use analytics providers such as Google Analytics to help us evaluate and measure the use and performance of our Site. To opt-out of the aggregation and analysis of data collected about you on our Site by Google Analytics, visit <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout> and download and install the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on.

  3. **Information We Obtain from Third Party Sources** We collect Personal Information from a number of third party sources.  
**Supplemental Information:** We may receive additional Personal Information from third party sources that we may append to existing consumer information, such as email and address verification and interest data. We use this supplemental information to better understand our consumers, deliver relevant offers and advertising, and improve our operations, Site and our advertising and marketing campaigns.

**Affiliate Program:** The Janie and Jack Affiliate Program enables third parties to refer customers to our Site in exchange for a commission. When you are referred to our site through our Affiliate Partners we will receive information about you, including Other Information in order to match your purchases to the Affiliate Partner’s referral. We collect, use and share this information to administer the Affiliate Program and to process transactions.

**Third Party Sharing Tools:** We may provide functionality on the Site that will allow you to share content or access third party sharing tools such as widgets, tools or buttons. If you choose to use these sharing functions, we will use your Personal Information and the information you  provide to share content only. As with all links to non-Janie and Jack Sites, content and services, we recommend that you read the privacy policies and terms associated with third parties carefully.

#### Additional Purposes For Which We Collect And Use Information

In addition to the uses described above, we may use your Personal Information for the following purposes: 

  * Operating our business;
  * Contacting you to respond to your requests or inquiries and provide customer support;
  * Contacting you about programs, products, or services that we believe may be of interest to you, new product or service announcements, savings awards, event invitations, or sharing with you special offers from other companies;
  * Providing you with personally tailored coupons, programs, promotional information, offers, and other information;
  * Serving you with personalized advertising on our Site and on other websites;
  * Conducting market research, surveys, and similar inquiries to help us understand trends and customer needs across product categories or customer groups;
  * Creating, improving and developing our products and services;
  * Administering our rewards programs including allowing you to create and maintain customer profiles, analyzing your interactions with us, presenting customized offers, and improving our products, services, programs, and other offerings;
  * Evaluating your shopping experience or existing products and services, or to create new items;
  * Alerting you about a product safety announcement or recall or correction of an offer, promotion, or advertisement;
  * Preventing, investigating, or providing notice of fraud, unlawful or criminal activity, or unauthorized access to or use of Personal Information, our website or data systems; or to meet legal obligations;
  * Investigating and resolving disputes and security issues and enforcing our Terms of Use and other agreements;
  * Sending you text messages or push notifications when you sign up for one of our messaging programs. These messages will be sent by automated means. Consent is not a condition of any purchase. You may opt out of a text message program by following the instructions in the " **Managing Your Communication Preferences** " section below; and
  * Any other lawful, legitimate business purpose.

#### When We May Share Information With Others

We share your Personal Information with third parties in the ways described in this Privacy Policy.

**Service Providers:** We share your Personal Information with third party service providers who complete transactions or perform services on our behalf or for your benefit, such as for payment processing, marketing, analytics, or to verify customer data, such as mailing addresses.

**Gap Inc. Brands:** We may share your information with legal entities in the Gap Inc. family of companies for purposes and uses that are consistent with this Privacy Policy. For example, we may share information between our brands to provide you with promotions of products and services that may be of interest to you.

**Affiliate Program:** We may share your information with our partners in the Janie and Jack Affiliate Program for the purpose of administering the programs, including the payment of applicable commissions.

**Business Partners:** We may partner with other companies and individuals with respect to particular products, services or marketing programs. Partners include our co-promotion partners for products that we jointly develop and/or market with other companies. Some Partners may collect information on our behalf on our Site. These third parties may be provided with access to Personal Information needed to perform their functions.

**Legal Process, Safety and Terms Enforcement:** We may disclose your Personal Information to legal or government regulatory authorities in response to their requests for such information or to assist in investigations. We may also disclose your Personal Information to third parties in connection with claims, disputes or litigation, when otherwise required by law, or if we determine its disclosure is necessary to protect the health and safety of you or us, or to enforce our legal rights or contractual commitments that you have made.

**Business Transfers:** Your Personal Information may be disclosed as part of a corporate business transaction, such as a merger,  acquisition, joint venture, or financing or sale of some or all of our company assets, including bankruptcy proceedings, and could be transferred to a third party as one of the business assets in such a transaction. It may also be disclosed in the event of insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership.

#### Your Online Choices

We support the self-regulatory principles of the Digital Advertising Alliance (" **DAA** "). We work with a variety of advertisers, advertising networks, advertising servers, and analytics companies (" **Ad Partners** ") that use different technologies to collect data about your use of the Site (such as pages visited, ads viewed or clicked on) in order to deliver relevant advertising.

These technologies may include the placement on our Site of cookies or web beacons, and other data collection technologies by these Ad Partners to track how our Site are being used, to track where users go and what they do after their leave our Site, and to link various devices you may use, and to serve you more relevant ads. These advertisements may appear on our Site or other services that you visit.

Our systems do not recognize browser “Do Not Track” signals. For more information about how Ad Partners use the information collected by the technologies on our Site and about your options not to accept cookies placed by some of these companies on our Site, please visit the [DAA’s opt-out page](http://optout.aboutads.info/#!/). You may also opt out of additional third party advertising networks by going to the Network Advertising Initiative’s [website](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/) and following the directions. If you are accessing the Site from the European Union, please visit the [EDAA’s opt-out page](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) and if you are accessing the Site from Canada, please visit the [DAAC’s opt-out page](http://youradchoices.ca/choices/).

The opt-outs described above are device- and browser-specific and may not work on all devices. If you choose to opt-out through any of these opt-out tools, this does not mean you will cease to see advertising. Rather, the ads you see will just not be based on your interests. In addition, when you opt out using one of these methods, our Ad Partners will continue to collect information for any other purpose permitted by the DAA’s rules. Since these opt-outs are cookie-based, if you clear your cookies at any time, you will need to opt out again through the links above.

#### How We Protect Children's Privacy

Janie and Jack is concerned about the safety and security of children. Our Site is intended for a general audience, and not targeted to or intended for use by children under 13. Accordingly, we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received  personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will take steps to delete that information from our records. If you are a parent or guardian that has knowledge that we have collected information from your child, please contact us to request removal at [ privacy@janieandjack.com](mailto:privacy@janieandjack.com). 

#### Links to Third Party Site

Please be aware that our Site may contain links to other websites hosted by third parties. Janie and Jack does not control and is not responsible for the  content or privacy practices and policies of such third party websites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site and to read the privacy policies of each and every third party website, especially if such websites collect personal information from you. 

#### Managing Your Communication Preferences

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. At any time, you may elect to discontinue receiving commercial messages from us or our sharing information with third parties for their marketing purposes by submitting an opt-out request to the contact information below or by following these instructions:

If you wish to opt out of receiving our email newsletters or promotions, you may do so at any time by clicking "unsubscribe" in any marketing email you receive from us and following the instructions on the screen. In addition, you can manage your email preferences by logging into your account at janieandjack.com and clicking on Customer Service - Email Preferences.

If you would like to opt out of receiving direct mail from Janie and Jack, you may do so by contacting us at 1-877-449-8800.

If you have consented to receive text messages, you may opt out of receiving them by using the method provided in the text message or by contacting us at the address below. 

#### Your California Privacy Rights

California residents may opt-out of Janie and Jack’s disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. As detailed above, California users may choose to opt-out of the sharing of personal information with third parties for marketing purposes at any time by submitting a request using the contact information below. We honor all such opt-out requests and it is our policy not to share personal information with third  parties for direct marketing purposes where you have submitted such a request. It is important to note that this opt-out does not prohibit disclosures made for non-marketing purposes. 

#### Accessing and Updating Your Information

You may review your Personal Information that is readily accessible through our Site or contact us to request that it be updated by using the contact information below. You have the right to request a copy of the information which we hold about you (for which we may charge you a small fee for large or complex requests). In addition, if you would like to access, verify, correct, update or delete your e-mail address, mailing address or other personal information with us please contact us directly. We will respond to your request within any legally required response time frame.

We will retain your Personal Information for as long as your account is active or as reasonably necessary for the purpose for which it was collected. We will retain and use your Personal Information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations or data retention policies, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. 

#### Security

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of information transmitted to us. However, no data transmission over the Internet or other network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect information transmitted on or through our Site, we cannot and do not guarantee the security of any information you transmit on or through the Site or Services, and you do so at your own risk. 

#### Processing in the United States

Please be aware that your Personal Information and communications may be transferred to and maintained on servers or databases located outside your state, province, or country. If you are located outside of the United States, please be advised that we process and store all information in the United States. The laws in the United States may not be as protective of your privacy as those in your location. By using the Site, you are agreeing to the collection, use, transfer, and disclosure of your Personal Information and communications will be governed by the applicable laws in the United States.

For the transfer of personal information to countries outside the EU, we have entered so-called “Standard Contractual Clauses” approved by the Commission of the European Union for international transfer of Personal Information to controllers or processors established in third countries as the case may be. 

#### For EU Residents

  1. **Your Rights**

If you are located in the EU, with respect to your Personal Information, you have the right to:

    * request access to and be provided with information on the processing of your Personal Information;
    * request corrections of your personal information if such Personal Information proves inaccurate or incomplete;
    * request your Personal Information to be deleted (i) if it is no longer necessary for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, (ii) should you decide to withdraw your consent where you gave it, (iii) should you object to its processing for direct marketing purposes, (iv) should you identify that it would have been unlawfully processed, (v) should we be under a legal obligation to erase it to comply with EU law or the law of an EU country and always provided we are not under a legal obligation to keep it;
    * restrict the processing of your Personal Information (i) if you contest its accuracy; (ii) if the processing is unlawful and you oppose the erasure; (iii) if it is no longer needed for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, but you require it for the establishment, exercise or defense of a legal claim, (iv) if you object to profiling;
    * object to the processing of your Personal Information for direct marketing purposes or to any processing which we based on our legitimate interest (e.g. profiling);
    * receive Personal Information which you provided to us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and to transmit it to another provider provided it is processed based on your consent or our contract;
    * lodge a complaint with your relevant data protection authority.

  2. **Our Legal Bases for Processing**

The legal basis for the processing of your Personal Information listed above is as follows:

As necessary for the performance of the contract between us to provide you with the products or services you requested or which we consider in our legitimate interests:

    * Operating our business;
    * Contacting you to respond to your requests or inquiries and provide customer support;
    * Contacting you about programs, products, or services that we believe may be of interest to you, new product or service announcements, savings awards, event invitations, or sharing with you special offers from other companies;
    * Providing you with personally tailored coupons, programs, promotional information, offers, and other information;
    * Conducting market research, surveys, and similar inquiries to help us understand trends and customer needs across product categories or customer groups;
    * Creating, improving and developing our products and services;
    * Administering our rewards programs including allowing you to create and maintain customer profiles, analyzing your interactions with us, presenting customized offers, and improving our products, services, programs, and other offerings;
    * Evaluating your shopping experience or existing products and services, or to create new items;
    * Alerting you about a product safety announcement or recall or correction of an offer, promotion, or advertisement;
    * Preventing, investigating, or providing notice of fraud, unlawful or criminal activity, or unauthorized access to or use of Personal Information, our website or data systems; or to meet legal obligations;
    * Investigating and resolving disputes and security issues and enforcing our Terms of Use and other agreements; and 
    * Any other lawful, legitimate business purpose.

Based on your voluntary consent:

    * Serving you with personalized advertising on our Site and on other websites;
    * Contacting you about programs, products, or services that we believe may be of interest to you, new product or service announcements, savings awards, event invitations, or sharing with you special offers from other companies;
    * Providing you with personally tailored coupons, programs, promotional information, offers, and other information;
    * Sending you text messages or push notifications when you sign up for one of our messaging programs. These messages will be sent by automated means. Consent is not a condition of any purchase. You may opt out of a text message program by following the instructions in the “Managing Your Communication Preferences” section below;

#### Changes to this Policy

Janie and Jack reserves the right to change, modify or amend this policy from time to time. We will post the changes here. Your continued use of our Site constitutes your agreement to abide by the policy as changed. If you object to any such changes, your sole recourse shall be to cease using our Site. 

#### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or other privacy-related matters, you may contact us in the following ways:  
Janie and Jack  
Customer Service  
2299 Kids Way  
Dixon, CA 95620  
Telephone: 1-877-449-8800  
E-mail: [privacy@janieandjack.com](mailto:privacy@janieandjack.com)
